<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Abrubrmqw</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Abrubrmqw</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 15:46:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abrubrmqw.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Actually Treat Other Believers Like Family</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/94868756-how-to-actually-treat-other-believers-like-family/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 15:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/94868756-how-to-actually-treat-other-believers-like-family/</guid><description>Some of the most beautiful words in Scripture are found in Romans 12:10. There Paul writes that we are to love one another like members of our own family. The picture he is describing here is that we should “warmly welcome” one another when we see each other (it’s not a polite, but awkward one arm hug), and then we should “make plans for the family feast in heaven” where we will all be together forever.</description></item><item><title>Is it My Responsibility to Help the Widows and Orphans?</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/89634257-is-it-my-responsibility-to-help-the-widows-and-orphans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 11:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/89634257-is-it-my-responsibility-to-help-the-widows-and-orphans/</guid><description>The scriptures are clear. The responsibility for the well-being of widows, fatherless children, and the indigent is on the shoulders of all who call themselves Christians, or believers. Many people are blinded by racism, lack of finances, and a lack ofeducation to its role in social reform. It is understood that no Christian can rescue a community from the ravages of poverty as they did two thousand years ago when Jesus walked the land, but still today the Christian can point others towards Christ through love and action, which is a reflection of Christ’s divine Love (Rom 5:1).</description></item><item><title>One Key Reason Why Church Consultations Fail</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/31696805-one-key-reason-why-church-consultations-fail/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:58:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/31696805-one-key-reason-why-church-consultations-fail/</guid><description>Church consultations have been an institution since the mid-1980s. They are a significant revenue stream for church consultants. However, these paid consulting assignments tend to be more profitable if they are short and provide only a few pages of recommendations; so consultants are under enormous pressure to sell their clients the shortest possible engagement in order to maximize revenues. The most cost-effective project that provides limited (or no) assistance is not one that many churches can afford.</description></item><item><title>Why Are There So Many Ideas about Heaven That Are Not Biblical?</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/29390386-why-are-there-so-many-ideas-about-heaven-that-are-not-biblical/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 08:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/29390386-why-are-there-so-many-ideas-about-heaven-that-are-not-biblical/</guid><description>A person's ideas about heaven are usually rooted in their understanding of who Jesus is. The Bible tells us that He is the way to the Father (John 14:6), and He is also our salvation (Hebrews 7:25). Understanding how He saved us gives us the right perspective on heaven; but it also allows us to understand why the Bible is so clear about how it gets into heaven, that is, we get there through Jesus Christ alone (Romans 6:23), by faith.</description></item><item><title>Why Pastors Struggle to Ask for Help (And How to Get Past It)</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/22580105-why-pastors-struggle-to-ask-for-help-and-how-to-get-past-it/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/22580105-why-pastors-struggle-to-ask-for-help-and-how-to-get-past-it/</guid><description>Many pastors are reluctant to ask for help. They often feel they need to do it all. Or, as if the problem isn’t a big deal. Or, that it will somehow appear too vulnerable or weak to even ask.
But in order for you to thrive as a leader–and fulfill your calling–you must learn how and when to ask for help. Why? The success of an organization depends on more than just the skills of its leader; it also relies upon the people and resources around them who can take some of the load off so that they can focus on doing what they’re supposed to be doing in the first place.</description></item><item><title>Why Do Christians Emphasize Hell Instead of Not Being with God in Heaven?</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/40887163-why-do-christians-emphasize-hell-instead-of-not-being-with-god-in-heaven/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/40887163-why-do-christians-emphasize-hell-instead-of-not-being-with-god-in-heaven/</guid><description>Many people believe that some people will go to a place called "Hell" after they die. They believe that the ones who will be tormented there are those who did not accept Jesus as their Savior. Many people wonder about this and why God would send anyone somewhere so horrible! I want to show you what the Bible actually says, because many people have been told wrong information on this topic.</description></item><item><title>Guilt and the Great Deception in the Christian Life</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/95658303-guilt-and-the-great-deception-in-the-christian-life/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 15:01:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/95658303-guilt-and-the-great-deception-in-the-christian-life/</guid><description>Guilt. It’s a part of the human condition, a reminder of our imperfection that we can never seem to get rid of or escape from no matter how hard we try. We have all experienced the debilitating effect that guilt can have on the soul that sins but is also longing for redemption. Whether it’s a matter of life and death, faiulre and accomplishment, sickness or health; in every realm of human existence we are reminded that there has been an exalted standard set forth by God Himself which was borne out in the life of His son Jesus Christ.</description></item><item><title>Why the Church Should Take Responsibility for Its Liberties and Freedoms</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/39911232-why-the-church-should-take-responsibility-for-its-liberties-and-freedoms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 13:43:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/39911232-why-the-church-should-take-responsibility-for-its-liberties-and-freedoms/</guid><description>The church is one of the most important institutions in society. It plays a vital role in promoting and protecting the rights of people. The church has a long history of defending freedom and liberties, which makes it an essential ally to democracy. In this article, we will explore why the church should take responsibility for its freedoms. We will look at some of the specific ways that the church can help defend freedom and discuss how it can contribute to creating a more just and equitable society.</description></item><item><title>Why People Are Losing Their Religion (and How the Church Can Respond)</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/32801936-why-people-are-losing-their-religion-and-how-the-church-can-respond/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 17:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/32801936-why-people-are-losing-their-religion-and-how-the-church-can-respond/</guid><description>The Gallup organization, which has been polling Americans about their views on a wide variety of issues every year for more than forty years, reveals that the trend in religious belief and practice over the last generation is unmistakable. The decline is real and has nothing to do with socio-economic factors or other such variables. In fact, this pattern is present across all demographic profiles. According to the study:
The current drop in U.</description></item><item><title>Why Should Christians Evaluate What Their Lives Are Built On?</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/41303061-why-should-christians-evaluate-what-their-lives-are-built-on/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/41303061-why-should-christians-evaluate-what-their-lives-are-built-on/</guid><description>Many Christians are living the Christian life with a desire to be obedient and faithful. As they go about their daily activities, there is often little evaluation of what type of foundation they have been building their lives on. Although we may not be actively involved in a building project, every person is building their lives with various materials from which they hope to gain security. Many of our lifestyles are lived as though there are no consequences.</description></item><item><title>What Does Jesus Teach Us about God's End-Times Plan?</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/69857738-what-does-jesus-teach-us-about-god-s-end-times-plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 21:32:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/69857738-what-does-jesus-teach-us-about-god-s-end-times-plan/</guid><description>Matthew 24 is often called the Olivet Discourse, because it tells us what Jesus taught on the Mount of Olives as He was answering questions asked by His disciples. In this chapter we read about some of these important matters including:
The destruction of Jerusalem (vs.2,16) The second coming and end of time (vs.3,30,36) The signs of this end (vs.5-8) At times in history this chapter has been used by many people as a blueprint to predicting when the world will come to an end and how it all will happen.</description></item><item><title>9 Lessons for New Christians ... And Old Ones</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/97001092-9-lessons-for-new-christians-and-old-ones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 09:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/97001092-9-lessons-for-new-christians-and-old-ones/</guid><description>Conversion to Christianity can be a terrifying experience; the early church leaders are often described as being “afraid” of becoming Christians. The first step is often one in which they flee from their previous lives and attempt to hide. For new converts, this fear can continue into their newly converted life. They feel like an imposter, afraid that someone will discover that they don’t know much (and really not much at all) about Christian doctrine.</description></item><item><title>Self-Care: Selfish Habit or Holy Endeavor?</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/93888946-self-care-selfish-habit-or-holy-endeavor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:49:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/93888946-self-care-selfish-habit-or-holy-endeavor/</guid><description>'So, which came first, the habit or the self-care?' This might sound like an odd question at a time when many are finding self-care is all they have to look forward to while under lockdown. Perhaps you associate it with a self-indulgent pastime - something that feeds a sense of pride and pleasure in one’s own body while neglecting others (if you’ll pardon this slight reductionist interpretation). While I recognize this may be true for some, my focus here is on why self-care is so important (and pleasurable), even if we disagree where it sits on the scale between the holy and the sinful.</description></item><item><title>The Good and the Bad of Christian Fundamentalism</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/81798171-the-good-and-the-bad-of-christian-fundamentalism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:52:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/81798171-the-good-and-the-bad-of-christian-fundamentalism/</guid><description>This study is based upon the premise that theological systems are good things, though they can be taken to extremes. Extremism in itself is not necessarily bad; but it becomes destructive when it prevents one from seeing or accepting any viewpoint other than his own.
It is our contention that some fundamentalists have become rigid in their thinking – in order to feel more secure and comfortable. To do so they have unthinkingly adopted a kind of "</description></item><item><title>4 Keys to Building Confidence in God When Life Falls Apart</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/48730705-4-keys-to-building-confidence-in-god-when-life-falls-apart/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 09:34:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/48730705-4-keys-to-building-confidence-in-god-when-life-falls-apart/</guid><description>Life is full of ups and downs, joys and sorrows, highs and lows. But when bad things happen, how do you hang onto your faith? When your world falls apart, how do you keep believing God loves you and that the trials are part of something bigger than you know? This week, I’m giving a special workshop to help equip you to be confident in God no matter what’s happening around you.</description></item><item><title>How Should Christians Approach Progress in Technology?</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/77275197-how-should-christians-approach-progress-in-technology/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 23:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/77275197-how-should-christians-approach-progress-in-technology/</guid><description>Technology is woven throughout our lives. Most of us are heavily vested in the progress made, especially with recent and upcoming technological advances. There is no doubt taht much of the technology we have today has significantly changed our day-to-day lives. The advancement of technology over time has led to an increase in comforts. There’s no question technology makes our lives better by some definition. However, if Christians aren’t careful about the way they view technology or science, it could lead them down a very slippery slope.</description></item><item><title>Why Christians Can Be Bad at Being Kind</title><link>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/61800566-why-christians-can-be-bad-at-being-kind/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 18:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abrubrmqw.github.io/posts/61800566-why-christians-can-be-bad-at-being-kind/</guid><description>Love is patient. Love is kind. It does not envy, it does not boast, it is not proud. It is not rude, it is not self-seeking, it is not easily angered, it keeps no record of wrongs.
1 Corinthians 13:4-5 NIV
There are times when I have felt like people don’t realize just how kind I can be! Well maybe not when I’m feeling mean and spiteful towards someone but even then … I need to reflect on that s tatement!</description></item></channel></rss>